Guide to the Trigant Burrow Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Main Correspondence File, 1875-1983; Series I; 20.25' (49 boxes)
  - Kempf, Edward J.(*), 1932-1945 (Box 20, Folder 502)
  - Kerr, William J., 1939, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 503)
  - Kessler, John J., 1945-1949 (Box 20, Folder 504)
  - Killiam, Mary Elizabeth, 1944-1948 (Box 20, Folder 505)
  - Kinder, Elaine Flitner(*), 1925-1948 (Box 20, Folder 506-514)
    See also: box 52, folder 1469-1472
  - Kindwall, Josef A.(*), 1931-1935 (Box 20, Folder 515)
  - Kirby, Daniel B.(*), 1932-1953 (Box 20, Folder 516-518)
  - Kirby, George H., 1927-1928 (Box 20, Folder 519)
  - Kirby, Sally, 1918-1932 (Box 20, Folder 520)
  - Kluckhohn, Clyde, 1948-1949 (Box 20, Folder 521)
  - Klyce, Scudder, 1927-1928 (Box 20, Folder 522)
  - Knopf, Alfred A., Inc., 1924-1950 (Box 20, Folder 523)
  - Korzybski, Alfred(*), 1925-1949 (Box 20, Folder 524-525)
  - Krogman, Wilton Marion(*), 1945-1949 (Box 20, Folder 526)
  - Kronick, Harry, 1936-1950 (Box 20, Folder 527)
  - Krutch, Joseph Wood, 1948-1949 (Box 20, Folder 528)
  - "L" general, 1925-1950, undated (Box 21, Folder 529-532)
  - La Dame, Mary(*), 1929-1938 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - La Garde, Richard D.(*), 1915-1950 (Box 21, Folder 534-547)
  - Lamb, Arthur, 1922-1924 (Box 22, Folder 548)
  - The Lancet, 1926, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 549)
  - Landis, Carney, 1948-1949 (Box 22, Folder 550)
  - Langhorne, Kate C.(*), 1925-1926 (Box 22, Folder 551)
  - Langhorne, W.H., 1926-1927 (Box 22, Folder 551)
  - Laning, J. Holcombe(*), 1945-1950 (Box 22, Folder 552)
  - Lanphier, Marion(*), 1938-1949 (Box 22, Folder 553)
  - Lashley, Karl S., 1935-1948 (Box 22, Folder 554)
  - Lasswell, Harold D., 1948-1949 (Box 22, Folder 554)
  - Lawrence, D. H.(*), 1926-1928 (Box 22, Folder 555)
  - Lawrenceville School(*), 1922 (Box 22, Folder 556)
  - Lay, Wilfrid, 1925, 1927 (Box 22, Folder 557)
  - Leary, Daniel B., 1938-1939, undated (Box 22, Folder 558)
  - Leigh, Helen L. Pease(*), 1925-1944 (Box 22, Folder 559-561)
  - Leigh, John Randolph(*), 1922-1949 (Box 22, Folder 562-570)
    See also: box 52, folder 1473
  - Lewis, Nolan D. C., 1935-1949 (Box 22, Folder 571)
  - Liddell, H. S., 1937, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 572)
  - The Lifwynn Foundation(*), 1927-1950 (Box 22, Folder 573)
  - Lillie, Ralph S.(*), 1935-1949 (Box 22, Folder 574)
  - Lindeman, Eduard C.(*), 1926-1949 (Box 22, Folder 575)
  - Lippincott, Helen(*), 1948-1949 (Box 22, Folder 576)
  - Lippmann, Walter, 1934-1949 (Box 22, Folder 577)
  - Little, James, 1941-1942 (Box 22, Folder 578)
  - Livermore, George R.(*), 1945-1950 (Box 22, Folder 579)
  - Locke, Agnes C.(*), 1926-1941 (Box 22, Folder 580-581)
  - Locke, Charles R.(*), 1925-1937 (Box 23, Folder 582)
  - Loeb, Philip(*), 1942-1943 (Box 23, Folder 583)
  - Long, A. R., Jr., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 584)
  - Long, Laura Burrow(*), 1928-1949 (Box 23, Folder 585)
  - Lopez, Ernani, 1943-1948 (Box 23, Folder 586)
  - The Lotus Club(*), 1938-1943 (Box 23, Folder 587)
  - Lowie, Robert H., 1948-1949 (Box 23, Folder 588)
  - Lyle, William Gordon, 1944-1950 (Box 23, Folder 589)
  - Lyman, David Russell(*), 1937-1952 (Box 23, Folder 590-592)
  - Lyon, A. A., 1922-1923 (Box 23, Folder 593)
  - "M" general, 1920-1957, undated (Box 23, Folder 594-599)
  - McClanahan, Robert, 1933-1947 (Box 23, Folder 600)
  - McCombs, A. Parks, 1942-1950 (Box 23, Folder 600)
  - MacCurdy, John T.(*), 1915-1934 (Box 23, Folder 601)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, Inc.(*), 1949-1950 (Box 23, Folder 602)
  - Macht, David I., 1940-1947 (Box 23, Folder 603)
  - MacIver, Robert M., 1935-1937 (Box 23, Folder 604)
  - McKibbin, Mary B.(*), 1924-1925 (Box 23, Folder 605)
  - McKnight, Richard J.(*), 1921-1950, undated (Box 23, Folder 606)
  - McLester, James S.(*), 1934-1948 (Box 23, Folder 607)
  - MacMartin, MacGregor, 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 608)
  - The MacMillan Company(*), 1922-1936 (Box 23, Folder 609-610)
  - The MacMillan Company, 1937-1941 (Box 24, Folder 611-617)
  - McRae, Nannie, 1926 (Box 24, Folder 618)
  - McWhirter, Lillian C.(*), 1938-1945 (Box 24, Folder 619)
  - Magoun, Richard M., 1948-1950 (Box 24, Folder 620)
  - Maier, Hans W., 1932-1933 (Box 24, Folder 620)
  - Malmo, Robert B., 1948-1949 (Box 24, Folder 621)
  - Malone, Margaret Bradford(*), 1941-1950 (Box 24, Folder 622)
  - Manny, Frank A.(*), 1925-1949, undated (Box 24, Folder 623)
  - Marcus, Joseph, 1928 (Box 24, Folder 624)
  - Marquis, The A. N. Company(*), 1927-1950 (Box 24, Folder 625-626)
  - Marquis, Donald G., 1939 (Box 24, Folder 627)
  - Mason, Donald B., 1941-1949 (Box 24, Folder 628)
  - Mason, Hildegard, 1941, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 628)
  - Mason, Ruth Putnam(*), 1926-1949 (Box 24, Folder 629)
  - Maury, Dabney H., 1939, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 629)
  - Mayne, Robert(*), 1942-1949 (Box 24, Folder 630-631)
  - Medical & Chirurgical Faculty of Maryland, 1927-1934 (Box 24, Folder 632)
  - Medical Journal and Record (*), 1925-1933 (Box 24, Folder 633)
  - Medical Society of the County of New York(*), 1929-1951 (Box 24, Folder 634)
  - Medical Society of the State of New York(*), 1927-1949 (Box 24, Folder 635)
  - Memoranda to Florida(*), 1937-1938 January (Box 24, Folder 636-637)
  - Memoranda to Florida, 1938 February-1940 (Box 25, Folder 638-651)
  - Mencken, Henry L., 1923-1948 (Box 25, Folder 652)
  - Menninger Clinic(*), 1926-1943 (Box 25, Folder 653)
  - Mental Health Society(*), 1925-1927 (Box 25, Folder 654)
  - Merrill, Clare
    See: box 60, folder 1691-1696
  - Meyer, Adolf(*), 1915-1948 (Box 25, Folder 655-659)
  - Meyer, Mary, 1920-1950 (Box 26, Folder 660)
  - Milburn, Janet F., 1937 (Box 26, Folder 661)
  - Millar, John H., 1942 (Box 26, Folder 662)
  - Miller, James G., 1948-1949 (Box 26, Folder 663)
  - The Mitre Press, 1937-1940 (Box 26, Folder 664)
  - Montavon, William F., 1938, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 665)
  - Moomaw, Ben C.(*), 1941-1950 (Box 26, Folder 666)
  - Moore, Mary Milligan(*), 1918-1950, undated (Box 26, Folder 667-680)
  - Moore, Merrill(*), 1941-1951 (Box 26, Folder 681)
  - Morgan, Abby B.(*), 1918-1932 (Box 26, Folder 682)
  - Morgan, C. Lloyd, 1934-1935 (Box 26, Folder 682)
  - Mott, Francis J.(*), 1940-1945 (Box 26, Folder 683)
  - Muller, Herbert J., 1948-1949 (Box 26, Folder 684)
  - Müller-Freienfels, Richard, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 685)
  - Murchison, Carl(*), 1927-1937 (Box 27, Folder 686)
  - Murfitt, Mary L., 1944-1949 (Box 27, Folder 687)
  - Murphy, Gardner(*), 1930-1949 (Box 27, Folder 688)
  - Murray, Miriam F.(*), 1923-1935 (Box 27, Folder 689)
  - Muster, A. J.(*), 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 690)
  - "N" general, 1924-1950 (Box 27, Folder 691-693)
  - Nagel, Hildegard(*), 1924-1949, undated (Box 27, Folder 694)
  - Nash, Lucia Devereux Smith(*), 1922-1950 (Box 27, Folder 695-700)
  - The Nation, 1924-1949 (Box 27, Folder 701)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene(*), 1923-1949 (Box 27, Folder 702)
  - The National Cyclopedia of American Biography (*), 1933-1939 (Box 27, Folder 703)
  - Nature, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 704)
  - Needhammer, Marion Louise(*), 1943 (Box 27, Folder 705)
  - Neil, Charles A., 1949 (Box 27, Folder 706)
  - Nelson, Mary C., 1921, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 706)
  - Der Nervenarzt, 1931-1932 (Box 27, Folder 707)
  - The Neurosis of Man (*), 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 708-711)
  - The Neurosis of Man, 1948-1950 (Box 28, Folder 712-713)
    See also: box 80, folder 2117-2134
  - The New Republic (*), 1918-1945 (Box 28, Folder 714)
  - New York Academy of Medicine(*), 1925-1932 (Box 28, Folder 715)
  - New York Academy of Sciences(*), 1930-1950 (Box 28, Folder 716)
  - New York Physicians Club(*), 1932-1934 (Box 28, Folder 717)
  - New York Southern Society, 1940, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 718)
  - New York State Board of Medical Examiners(*), 1926-1929 (Box 28, Folder 719)
  - New York Times (*), 1925-1949 (Box 28, Folder 720)
  - The Newberry Library, 1948-1949 (Box 28, Folder 721)
  - Norfolk, Virginia, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 722)
  - Norton, W. W. & Company, Inc., 1927-1947 (Box 28, Folder 723)
  - Norwalk General Hospital, 1939-1950 (Box 28, Folder 724)
  - Norwich State Hospital, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 724)
  - "O" general, 1920-1949, undated (Box 28, Folder 725)
  - Oberndorf, Clarence Paul(*), 1925-1954 (Box 28, Folder 726)
    See also: box 1, folder 25
  - Odegard, Ornulv(*), 1948-1950 (Box 28, Folder 727)
  - Odell, Albert G., 1937 (Box 28, Folder 727)
  - Office memoranda(*), 1931-1939 (Box 28, Folder 728)
  - Ogburn, William F.(*), 1925-1949 (Box 28, Folder 729)
  - Ogden, C. K.(*), 1926-1957 (Box 28, Folder 730-733)
    See also: box 43, folder 1139
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1948-1950 (Box 28, Folder 734)
  - Osborn, Henry Fairfield, 1932, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 734)
  - Overholser, Winfred, 1944-1949 (Box 28, Folder 735)
  - "P" general, 1908-1950, undated (Box 28, Folder 736-740)
  - Page, John Randolph(*), 1936-1950 (Box 29, Folder 741)
  - Palmer, Gretta(*), 1943-1949 (Box 29, Folder 742)
  - Parker, Cornelia St[illegible]atton, 1925-1926 (Box 29, Folder 743)
  - Parker, Eleanor Gordon, 1920-1921 (Box 29, Folder 744)
  - Parker, Elizabeth W.(*), 1922-1933, undated (Box 29, Folder 745)
  - Parker, Robert Allerton, 1938, 1941 (Box 29, Folder 746)
  - Parr, Grace Whitford(*), 1936-1950 (Box 29, Folder 747-755)
  - Parsons, Talcott, 1948-1949 (Box 29, Folder 756)
  - Pathfinder (*), 1948-1949 (Box 29, Folder 757)
  - Paton, Stewart(*), 1927-1938 (Box 29, Folder 758)
  - Patry, Frederick L., 1934-1945 (Box 29, Folder 759)
  - Patterson, Robert J., 1947-1949 (Box 29, Folder 760)
  - Pattison, Blanch, 1936-1937 (Box 29, Folder 761)
  - Payson, Armour P.(*), 1926-1939 (Box 29, Folder 762)
  - Pease, Helen L.
    See: box 22, folder 559-561
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1937-1950 (Box 29, Folder 763)
  - Phi Delta Theta (Box 29, Folder 763)
  - Philosophy of Science Association(*), 1935-1948 (Box 29, Folder 764)
  - The Phoenix, 1938-1939 (Box 29, Folder 765)
  - Physicians Hospital, Plattsburgh, N. Y.(*), 1939 (Box 29, Folder 766)
  - Piotrowski, Zygmunt(*), 1935-1941 (Box 29, Folder 767)
  - Podolsky, Edward, 1941-1949 (Box 29, Folder 768)
  - Pope, Arthur Upham(*), 1946-1949 (Box 29, Folder 769)
  - Pope, Laura Spencer Portor(*), 1905-1950 (Box 30, Folder 770-775)
  - Powell, Francis, 1914-1946 (Box 30, Folder 776)
  - Psyche (*), 1926-1930 (Box 30, Folder 777)
  - Psychoanalytic Review (*), 1918-1945 (Box 30, Folder 778)
  - Psychological Bulletin, 1926, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 779)
  - Psychosomatic Medicine (*), 1939-1943 (Box 30, Folder 780)
  - "Q" general, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 781)
  - "R" general, 1922-1950 (Box 30, Folder 782-786)
  - Rand, Florence(*), 1923-1941 (Box 30, Folder 787)
  - Randall, Wyatt W., 1929 (Box 30, Folder 788)
  - Rashevsky, Nicholas(*), 1947-1949 (Box 30, Folder 789)
  - Raven, Alice(*), 1929-1939 (Box 30, Folder 790-791)
  - Read, Herbert(*), 1944-1950 (Box 30, Folder 792-795)
  - Rees, J. R.(*), 1935-1949 (Box 30, Folder 796)
  - Reilly, Marjorie E. Young(*), 1928-1949 (Box 30, Folder 797)
    See also: box 61, folder 1706-1709
  - Reprints inscribed, undated (Box 30, Folder 798)
  - Reymert, Martin Luther(*), 1947-1948 (Box 30, Folder 799)
  - Reymert, Martin Luther, 1948-1950, undated (Box 31, Folder 800-801)
  - Rhineberger, Margaret B., 1945-1947 (Box 31, Folder 802)
  - Roback, A. A., 1926-1937 (Box 31, Folder 803)
  - Roberts, Morley(*), 1934-1938 (Box 31, Folder 804)
  - Robinson, G. Canby, 1932-1936 (Box 31, Folder 805)
  - Robinson, James Harvey(*), 1923-1926, undated (Box 31, Folder 806)
  - Rogers, Carl R., 1948-1949 (Box 31, Folder 807)
  - Roland Park Country School, 1922-1924 (Box 31, Folder 808)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1939-1947, undated (Box 31, Folder 809)
  - Rosenberg Foundation(*), 1948-1949 (Box 31, Folder 810)
  - Rosenberg, Max L.(*), 1921-1930, undated (Box 31, Folder 811)
  - Rosenshine, Annette, 1925, undated (Box 31, Folder 812)
  - Routledge and Kegan Paul(*), 1947-1949 (Box 31, Folder 813-814)
  - Rowland, John Howard(*), 1929-1948 (Box 31, Folder 815-817)
  - Rukeyser, Muriel(*), 1943-1951 (Box 31, Folder 818)
  - Rusk, George Yeisley(*), 1929-1950 (Box 31, Folder 819)
  - Rusk, William Sener, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 819)
  - Russell, Bertrand, 1926, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 820)
  - "S" general (Sa - Sp), 1910-1950, undated (Box 31, Folder 821-826)
  - "S" general (St - Sz), 1919-1949, undated (Box 32, Folder 827-828)
  - Sancton, Thomas(*), 1949-1950 (Box 32, Folder 829)
  - Sandall, Mary, 1927-1928 (Box 32, Folder 830)
  - Sankaran, C. R., 1949-1950 (Box 32, Folder 831)
  - Sargent, Porter(*), 1932-1949 (Box 32, Folder 832)
  - Sawhill, John Eldon(*), 1944-1950 (Box 32, Folder 833)
  - Scheetz, Catherine O., 1924 (Box 32, Folder 834)
  - Scheetz, Estelle O., 1925-1935 (Box 32, Folder 835)
  - Scheetz, Oliver R.(*), 1923-1926 (Box 32, Folder 835)
  - Scheetz, Oliver D., 1924, 1926, undated (Box 32, Folder 836)
  - Scheetz, Raymond, 1923 (Box 32, Folder 836)
  - Schlesinger, Halle S.(*), 1927-1930 (Box 32, Folder 837)
  - Schmalhausen, Samuel D., 1932, 1934 (Box 32, Folder 838)
  - Schroeder, Theodore, 1927, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 839)
  - Schweizer Archiv für Neurologie und Psychiatrie (*), 1932, 1934 (Box 32, Folder 840)
  - Science, 1938, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 841)
  - Science Service(*), 1924-1942 (Box 32, Folder 842)
  - "Scientia"(*), 1934-1935 (Box 32, Folder 843)
  - The Scientific Monthly (*), 1924-1947 (Box 32, Folder 844)
  - Scovill, Florence M., 1935 (Box 32, Folder 845)
  - Scripture, May K.(*), 1920-1936 (Box 32, Folder 846)
  - Sebes-Syz, Lilly, 1938-1949 (Box 32, Folder 847)
  - Selling, Lowell S.(*), 1933-1945 (Box 32, Folder 848)
  - Shackleford, Elizabeth Burrow(*), 1935-1948 (Box 32, Folder 849-854)
  - Shames, Max(*), 1947-1949 (Box 32, Folder 855)
  - Shield, Albert B., 1934-1935 (Box 32, Folder 856)
  - Shields, Clarence(*), 1925-1943 (Box 32, Folder 857-859)
    See also: box 52, folder 1475
    See also: box 99, folder 2474-2484
  - Shields, Clarence, 1944-1950, undated (Box 33, Folder 860-861)
  - Shortlidge, R. J., 1920-1933 (Box 33, Folder 862)
  - Shott, Marian E.(*), 1923-1924 (Box 33, Folder 863)
  - Shoup, Homer B.(*), 1942-1947 (Box 33, Folder 864)
  - Sigerist, Henry Ernest, 1933-1957 (Box 33, Folder 865)
  - Sill, Alfreda
    See: box 13, folder 309-313
  - Sill, Alfreda Payson, 1926-1950 (Box 33, Folder 866-873)
  - Sill, Jane B.
    See: box 4, folder 84
  - Sill, Margaret
    See: box 43, folder 1135
  - Silver, Cassius D.(*), 1927-1949 (Box 33, Folder 874)
  - Simrall, Josephine D., 1925-1933 (Box 33, Folder 875)
  - Smaldone, Gerald(*), 1942-1949 (Box 33, Folder 876)
  - Smith, Charles Gordon, 1938-1950 (Box 33, Folder 877)
  - Smith, Eva(*), 1921-1930 (Box 33, Folder 878)
  - Smith, Lucia Devereux
    See: box 27, folder 695-700
  - Smithwick, Fanita M.(*), 1918-1950 (Box 33, Folder 879-884)
  - Smithwick, Graham(*), 1921-1931 (Box 33, Folder 885)
  - Snyder, R. Garfield, 1930-1934 (Box 33, Folder 886)
  - The Social Basis of Consciousness (*), 1927-1928, undated (Box 34, Folder 887-899)
    See also: box 65, folder 1849
    See also: box 72, folder 1972-2003
    See also: box 95, folder 2434
  - Sociological Review (*), 1926-1937 (Box 34, Folder 900)
  - Sorokin, Pitirim A.(*), 1929-1955 (Box 34, Folder 901)
  - Southern Medical Association(*), 1924-1948 (Box 34, Folder 902)
  - Southern Society for Philosophy and Psychology(*), 1926-1950 (Box 34, Folder 903)
  - Spalding, Katharine(*), 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 904)
  - Spillman, Ramsay(*), 1945-1948 (Box 34, Folder 905)
  - Spindle, Richard Buckner, Jr.(*), 1932-1941 (Box 34, Folder 906)
    See also: box 55, folder 1543-1546
  - Sporbert, Curtis P., 1946-1950 (Box 34, Folder 907)
  - Stace, Walter T., 1948-1949 (Box 34, Folder 908)
  - Stacy, Mary, 1945-1946 (Box 34, Folder 908)
  - Station WQYR, 1941-1945 (Box 34, Folder 909)
  - Stein, Fred M.(*), 1947-1950 (Box 34, Folder 910)
  - Stein, Leo(*), 1918-1947 (Box 34, Folder 911-917)
  - Steinbrocker, Otto(*), 1945-1949 (Box 34, Folder 918)
  - Stewart, John Quincy, 1948, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 919)
  - Stern, Adolf
    See: box 1, folder 24-25
  - Stragnell, Gregory(*), 1926-1945 (Box 34, Folder 920)
  - Strass, Herbert W.(*), 1934-1949 (Box 35, Folder 921)
  - Stratton, Alice Elenore(*), 1927-1949 (Box 35, Folder 922)
  - Stratton, George M.(*), 1908-1949 (Box 35, Folder 923)
  - Sullivan, Harry Stack(*), 1924-1939 (Box 35, Folder 924)
  - The Survey (*), 1923-1928 (Box 35, Folder 925)
  - Svenzon, Gunnar(*), 1947-1950 (Box 35, Folder 926)
  - Swisher, Walter S.(*), 1925-1928 (Box 35, Folder 927)
  - Syz, Emily Sherwood Burrow(*), 1922-1950, undated (Box 35, Folder 928-940)
  - Syz, Hans C.(*), 1923-1927 May (Box 35, Folder 941-943)
    See also: box 52, folder 1476-1487
  - Syz, Hans C., 1927 August-1935 September (Box 36, Folder 944-966)
  - Syz, Hans C., 1935 September-1939 February (Box 37, Folder 967-988)
  - Syz, Hans C., 1939 March-1950 (Box 38, Folder 989-1005)
  - Syz, John, 1926-1942 (Box 38, Folder 1006)
  - Syz, Clara (Box 38, Folder 1006)
  - "T" general, 1921-1950, undated (Box 38, Folder 1007-1010)
  - Tansley, A. G.(*), 1926-1928 (Box 38, Folder 1011)
  - Taylor, Quintard(*), 1930-1950 (Box 38, Folder 1012)
  - Tedesche, Sidney S.(*), 1925-1934 (Box 38, Folder 1013)
  - Thayer, Ellen(*), 1921-1939 (Box 38, Folder 1014-1017)
  - Thayer, Frank Marshall, 1940, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 1018)
  - Thew, Elsie G., 1946 (Box 39, Folder 1019)
  - Thieme Verlag(*), 1928-1939 (Box 39, Folder 1020-1021)
  - Thomas, William I., 1926, 1932 (Box 39, Folder 1022)
  - Thompson, Charles Baker(*), 1922-1935 July (Box 39, Folder 1023-1047)
    See also: box 53, folder 1488-1494
  - Thompson, Charles Baker, 1935 August-1939 July (Box 40, Folder 1048-1069)
  - Thompson, Charles Baker, 1939 August-1949, undated (Box 41, Folder 1070-1086)
  - Thompson, Marion A.(*), undated (Box 41, Folder 1087)
  - Thornton, Rosalie(*), 1929-1950 (Box 41, Folder 1088-1089)
  - Thouless, Robert H., 1926-1949 (Box 41, Folder 1090)
  - Tiebout, Harry M., 1928-1940 (Box 41, Folder 1091)
  - Tilley, Reade, Jr.(*), 1937-1943 (Box 41, Folder 1092)
  - Tilley, Mrs. Reade (Box 41, Folder 1092)
  - Tomlinson, Albin A.(*), 1922-1949 (Box 41, Folder 1093-1095)
  - Townshend, John G., 1928-1948 (Box 41, Folder 1096)
  - Traeger, Cornelius, 1930-1949 (Box 41, Folder 1097)
  - Train, John K., 1946-1949 (Box 41, Folder 1098)
  - Trench, Lilian, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 1098)
  - Tucker, Beverly R., 1937-1942 (Box 41, Folder 1099)
  - Twinem, Francis Patton(*), 1938-1944 (Box 41, Folder 1100-1101)
  - Twinem, Elizabeth (Box 41, Folder 1100-1101)
  - Twinem, Francis Patton, 1945-1950 (Box 42, Folder 1102-1103)
  - Twinem, Elizabeth (Box 42, Folder 1102-1103)
  - "U" general, 1920-1950 (Box 42, Folder 1104)
  - Ulman, Ella(*), 1925-1948 (Box 42, Folder 1105)
  - UNESCO(*), 1949-1950 (Box 42, Folder 1106)
  - United States. Treasury Department, 1927-1937 (Box 42, Folder 1107)
  - "V" general, 1928-1949 (Box 42, Folder 1108)
  - Guggenheimer, Aimée, 1934-1950 (Box 42, Folder 1109-1110)
  - Vaillant, Paula(*) (Box 42, Folder 1109-1110)
  - Van Kleeck, Mary(*), 1928-1934 (Box 42, Folder 1111)
  - Vandervoort, Jules(*), 1941-1949 (Box 42, Folder 1112)
  - Virginia, University of(*), 1930-1950 (Box 42, Folder 1113-1114)
  - "The Virginians"(*), 1936-1950 (Box 42, Folder 1115)
  - Voegtlin, Carl, 1928-1939 (Box 42, Folder 1116)
  - Voegtlin, Lilian (Box 42, Folder 1116)
  - von Bertalanffy, Ludwig(*), 1935-1949 (Box 42, Folder 1117)
  - von Wyss, Walter H., 1928-1938 (Box 42, Folder 1118)
  - "W" general, 1922-1950, undated (Box 42, Folder 1119-1123)
  - Wallace, Fannie D.(*), 1936-1941 (Box 42, Folder 1124)
  - Wallace, Kevin(*), 1948-1949 April (Box 42, Folder 1125-1126)
  - Wallace, Kevin, 1949 May - 1952 (Box 43, Folder 1127-1128)
  - Wallach, Jane(*), 1923-1946 (Box 43, Folder 1129)
  - Waring, J. Mowton S.(*), 1936-1938 (Box 43, Folder 1130)
  - Washington Psychoanalytic Society(*), 1925-1927 (Box 43, Folder 1131)
  - Washington University, School of Medicine, 1941, 1943 (Box 43, Folder 1132)
  - Watson, Goodwin B., 1930-1941 (Box 43, Folder 1133)
  - Watson, Virginia C.(*), 1926-1949 (Box 43, Folder 1134)
  - Weatherly, Margaret Sill(*), 1944-1950 (Box 43, Folder 1135)
  - Weaver, Warren, 1948-1949 (Box 43, Folder 1136)
  - Weber, Helen Aimee(*), 1924-1927 (Box 43, Folder 1137)
  - Webster, Charles
    See: box 54, folder 1519-1537
  - Wechsler, E. Barbara(*), 1933-1935 (Box 43, Folder 1138-1141)
  - Weinberg, Albert K.(*), 1926-1949 (Box 43, Folder 1142)
  - Weinberg, Anita (Box 43, Folder 1142)
  - Welch, Fay(*), 1925-1949 (Box 43, Folder 1143)
  - Wells, Guy H., 1939-1940 (Box 43, Folder 1144)
  - Wells, Harry K., 1937, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 1145)
  - Wertheimer, F. I., 1926-1935 (Box 43, Folder 1146)
  - Westcott, Edith C.(*), 1937 (Box 43, Folder 1147)
  - White, William Alanson(*), 1922-1937, undated (Box 43, Folder 1148)
  - Whitford, Grace
    See: box 29, folder 747-755
  - Whitman, Howard, 1949 (Box 43, Folder 1149)
  - Whittle, Henry Lyman, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 1150)
  - Wholey, Cornelius C.(*), 1922-1951 (Box 43, Folder 1151-1155)
  - Who's Who Among Physicians and Surgeons, 1937-1938 (Box 43, Folder 1156)
  - Who's Who in American Education, 1941, 1949 (Box 43, Folder 1157)
  - Who's Who in the East, 1940-1946 (Box 43, Folder 1158)
  - Who's Who in New York, 1937-1938 (Box 43, Folder 1158)
  - Whyte, Lance L.(*), 1927-1948 (Box 43, Folder 1159)
  - Wickham, Winfield M., 1937-1944 (Box 43, Folder 1160)
  - Wickser, Philip J., 1926-1944 (Box 43, Folder 1161)
  - Wieman, Regina Westcott, 1936-1938 (Box 43, Folder 1161)
  - Willcox, Louise Collier(*), 1922-1930 (Box 43, Folder 1162-1163)
  - Williams College, 1922-1923 (Box 44, Folder 1164)
  - Williams, Susan Adger(*), 1922-1924 (Box 44, Folder 1165)
  - Williams, Tom A., 1946 (Box 44, Folder 1166)
  - Wilson, Edna Bruns, 1936-1948 (Box 44, Folder 1167)
  - Winsor, Max(*), 1926-1934 (Box 44, Folder 1168)
  - Winternitz, Milton C., 1934-1935 (Box 44, Folder 1169)
  - Wise, Fannie, 1949-1950 (Box 44, Folder 1170)
  - Wolf, Heinrich F.(*), 1937-1949 (Box 44, Folder 1171)
  - Wolf, Miriam M. Bredow(*), 1933-1949 (Box 44, Folder 1172-1173)
  - Wolfe, Edwin R., 1926, 1933 (Box 44, Folder 1174)
  - Wondolowski, Charles A.(*), 1940-1950 (Box 44, Folder 1175-1178)
  - Wood, Harry W.(*), 1924-1925 (Box 44, Folder 1179)
  - Wood, Virginia H., 1923-1949 (Box 44, Folder 1180)
  - Woodger, J. H., 1936-1949 (Box 44, Folder 1180)
  - Woolf, Samuel, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 1181)
  - Woolford, Mason H.(*), 1925-1933 (Box 44, Folder 1182)
  - Wright, Madeline, 1922-1925 (Box 44, Folder 1183)
  - "Y" general, 1925-1949 (Box 44, Folder 1184)
  - Yerkes, Robert Mearns(*), 1928-1949 (Box 44, Folder 1185)
  - Yochum, Margaret Ozias Scheetz(*), 1923-1947 (Box 44, Folder 1186)
  - Young, Hugh Hampton(*), 1926-1939 (Box 44, Folder 1187)
  - Young, Kimball(*), 1925-1948 (Box 44, Folder 1188)
  - Young Men's Christian Association(*), 1946-1950 (Box 44, Folder 1189)
  - "Z" general, 1923-1949 (Box 44, Folder 1190)
  - Zeitschrift für die gesamte Neurologie und Psychiatre, 1929-1933 (Box 44, Folder 1191)
  - Zentralblatt für Psychotherapie (*), 1930-1933 (Box 44, Folder 1192)
  - Ziegler, Lloyd H., 1934-1944 (Box 44, Folder 1193)
  - Ziegler, Maurice, 1918-1919 (Box 44, Folder 1193)
  - Letters to Burrow and Shields during European trip, 1925 July-August (Box 44, Folder 1194-1196)
  - Letters to Burrow and Shields during European trip, 1925 September-October (Box 45, Folder 1197-1199)
  - Burrow, Trigant: wills, 19-9-50 (Box 45, Folder 1200)
  - Burrow, Trigant: obituary notices, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 1201)
  - Letters of sympathy, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 1202-1207)
  - Burrow ancestry, undated (Box 45, Folder 1208)
  - Burrow, Trigant: licenses and certificates, 1907-1927 (Box 45, Folder 1209)
    See also: box 100, folder 2490-2495